Hi, I'm Renca Miyamoto.
I'm Renca Miyamoto.
I'm here in Akihabara today.
Why did I come to Akihabara?
I came to buy a computer.
I'm using a regular PC now, but
I want to make my own PC.
by myself
I have a longing to build my own PC
I'd like to go to a store to buy
I'm going to go to the store and gather various materials.
I'll be back soon.
Thank you for watching!
Yes, that's why I'm here at NOSPALA Akihabara Honten.
I've really only bought PCs that are already finished,
I've never been to a place where there are so many small parts,
I have never been in a space full of small parts like this, but there are a lot of things that look familiar to me that I might need when I assemble it,
I have no idea what they are, though,
When was the last time I bought a PC?
How many years ago was it?
I don't even know what it is, but I don't know when I bought a PC,
I was shocked when I found out.
Such a cute PC.
A PC is like a huge object.
That's why I originally had all my devices in black,
But then I realized,
I noticed that the keyboard and mouse were white, too,
I have all my devices in white,
So I'd like to use bright colors for the PC, since it's all black now,
I'm not sure what to do,I'm a little unsure about anything,
I would like to ask someone at the store.
Thank you very much.
So, this is your first time to build your own PC,
First of all,
What do you think is the best part of building your own PC?
I think the best part of building your own PC is its appearance,
So I would like to decide on the appearance.
So I would like to decide on the appearance of the PC.
Yes.
Wow.
Oh.
I used to have a Logitech keyboard.
Now I bought it.
I went with the 60% keyboard Wootin.
I'm a balalant player.
It's this really cute light blue color.
The pink one has so many hearts and stuff inside, can you see them?
See, too cute.
It's fun just to get them all together.
I can't decide.
What color would be best?
But I think I'll go with white.
Okay, I see. Then, let's decide on this case as a base.
Please take care of it.
Okay, next, let's decide on the most important part of the computer, the CPU.
What is the intended use of the computer? What will you be using the computer for this time?
Mainly for FPS games.
What titles do you play most often?
Vallorant.
Vallorant. Thank you very much.
Do you want to use this computer as an opportunity to distribute your games, or even edit videos?
Uh, yes. I don't know, but yes.
Let's think about it in anticipation of the future.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
This CPU has a great impact on the overall performance of a PC, not to mention games,
But also for normal video editing.
The higher the performance of the CPU, the more efficient the work can be.
Since you mentioned that you are planning to use it for video distribution, we highly recommend Intel's Core i7 CPU.
Yes, I would recommend Intel's Core i7 CPU.
Is that correct?
Yes, that's fine.
Yes, thank you very much.
Okay, then, the graphics board.
Yes, I am sure.
Graphics board is specifically for games this time, so I would like to look at the performance of the graphics board.
Yes, that's right.
So, I would like to consider how comfortable you would like to play the game performance.
Apex Legend is a game that requires high specs, and there are a lot of shooting games in this area.
Oh, yes.
Yes. Since the client wanted to dye the graphics board white, we decided to use the 4.70Ti, which allows the graphics board to be white as well, so the inside can be unified in white.
This 4.70Ti is the latest graphics board.
The latest. This is it. It's white and cute. It's the latest.
Yes, it is.
Huh. Huh.
This way then.
Yes, please.
Yes, thank you.
Amazing. Look at that, it's designed like a Splatoon.
A motherboard is the foundation of a computer.
Various parts are attached to these parts and assembled together.
Are there any differences in design?
Are there differences not only in design but also in specifications?
Yes, there are. The larger motherboards are more expandable, so you can install more SSDs (storage media) and other parts.
This Athlon Z790 Live Mixer has 20 USB ports.
Wow, that's amazing.
Some of them can use quite a lot of USB ports.
I see.
Motherboards have their own strengths and weaknesses, depending on what you are using them for.
Cute.
B760M from Athlon, here.
Next, CPU fan. I mentioned earlier that the CPU is the brain of a human being, and this is the part that cools it down.
CPU fan. There are two major types: water-cooled and air-cooled.
There are two types: water-cooled and air-cooled.
There are two types: one cools the CPU with air and the other with water. The water-cooled type takes longer to assemble, but the water-cooled type is cool because you can clearly see the inside of the computer.
Oh, I see. The water-cooled type is the one that shines so brightly, isn't it?
That's right. The head of this part.
I see. But it seems to take a little time to assemble. Well, I don't know what to do. It looks modern, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Hmmm...
Well, the graphics board is a shiny type, so I'm going to match it.
Make it glow.
Water-cooling is also an option, since it is easy to assemble.I can make it shine, and water-cooling is also an option because it is easy to assemble.
But since I'm going to go through the trouble, I'm going to try my best to assemble it.
Water-cooling.
Yes, I'll go for water-cooling.
Shall we go with water-cooling?
I'll try. Yes, please.
Yes, please.
For water-cooling, I would recommend the other LS520.
Amazing.
Amazing Rainbow.
Yes.
This is it. This time, I'll use this white part. I'll take care of it. It's cute.
Wow, there are so many. Oh, I see. There are many kinds.
The glowing one. The glowing one. Yes, I see. Thank you very much. I'll take it, please.
250GB to the most expensive one. The current one is 2TB. 2TB.
No, but I'm the kind of person who likes to have a lot of capacity.
Speed 7000. 7000. Very fast. I definitely prefer this one.
Yes, it's SF. Yes, it's sci-fi.
Yes, so I have purchased it successfully,
Um, I'm going to go to the other room and finally assemble it. I'll do my best.
Okay, so here we are.
This is how it looks now.
I have all my purchases lined up like this.
I'm sure everyone will think, "Oh, I'm so excited!
I'm sure everyone will think
What is that background?
It's like a goth background.
Isn't it amazing? Isn't it amazing?
I'll start with something big.
I wonder if it's okay if I don't know anything about it.
Open it with a cutter.
It's heavy! It's pretty heavy.
I guess it is.
Hey! I remember now!
When I bought the PC, it was super hard to carry it to the living room by myself.
What? It's in the box one by one.
I'm sure I'd lose them.
What the heck.
We did this kind of thing in technology class, right?
Yeah.
It looks like the latest drone.
It's got something on it.
It's really heavy.
It's about the size of a super big watermelon.
So, once I opened the package, it's done.
And here is the side.
Oh my god. So many.
So all of this is inside here, and one PC is completed.
Well, I'd like to start assembling it,
For now, I'm going to read some kind of manual.
I'll read it.
Why English? Why Japanese?
I don't know, so I'd like to ask you.
I'm sorry, I don't know anything about it.
I'm sorry, but I don't know anything about it, and I'd really appreciate it if you could tell me.
What should I do first?
Yes, you need to put on gloves before you assemble.Yes, sir. We'll need gloves to put it all together.
You wear gloves?
Because the parts are vulnerable to static electricity.
I see.
Let's put on the gloves and start assembling.
Yes, sir.
Okay, here we go.
Mother Ford, CPU.
CPU
We're going to cut out the brain of the computer.
Yes, sir.
Let's raise it up.
That's it.
Wow.
One push, then shift.
there you go. oh, it's so tight
Oh, there you go.
I'll go put this in.
Wow, just like in school.
This is very important.
It has to be facing the right way.
You have to be a little careful with the direction.
I see.
Please be careful when you place it according to the direction.
Put it down slowly.
And then?
Yes, sir.
Close it?
Yes, I'll close it.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Is everything all right?
Yes, the black part comes off by itself.
That's right.
Yuck!
Ew! Ew!
Unh!
Is that right? Yes, it's the right one.
It sounded like it was broken. Oh, it's off!
It's done! I got it.
That's fun. Then the SSD.
SSD, 2TB, right? Yes, 2TB.
Yes, 2TB! Yes, I increased the capacity! It's so thin!
It's very thin like this.
Like a candy bar
Yes, like a candy bar
Yes, like this
Like this
Yes... in that direction.
Yes, sir.
And screw it on.
Oh, I see, so it's a screw.
Good luck!
I don't mind detail work.
Oh, is that right?
Is it closed?
Yes, it's closed.
It's not coming up, is it?
Yes, it's fine.
It's all right. I'm fine.
All right. - All right.
Heavy.
The latch is closed.
Can you open the sides, please?
Can I just open it normally?
Yes, I'm fine.
Oh, wow! That's great!
It takes a lot of strength.
One side at a time.
Oh, really!
Oh, I'm scared!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's okay.
It closes on its own.
Okay, let's continue with the installation.
Let's go ahead and install the parts inside the case.
Oh, no!
The first memorable part!
Back panel
Do it until you hear a click.
What?
Oh no, I'm not strong enough!
I wonder if this part is so hard to do.
It's so hard!
I'm going to break my finger.
I'm gonna break my finger!
Oh, I did it!Ah, it's done!
Done!
It's done!
Koukou
I see.
I think I can do it.
I'm good.
There are screws on the motherboard.
You just need to put on the same shape of screws from here.
Okay.
I can't do it.
It's like an amazing factory.
Gestalt fork is going to happen.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
I won't miss it.
Okay, okay.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Is that not right?
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Six?
Six.
All right, we're ready.
We're going to need you to install the water-cooling parts.
Yes, water cooling.
Oh, I see. That's where you're putting it.
Kaaan.
It's good!
Okay, we have 4 parts.
Now I'd like to put the fan on this side.Now I would like to put a fan on this side.
Yes, sir.
It's very easy to put it on if you put it on the opposite side.
I see.
Next, I'll put it on the lower right side.
It's on, it's on, it's on.
Okay, you got it.
Okay.
Now we're going to install the water cooling system into the case.
We're going to hold it down with the wind and screw it in from the top.
I see.
I used too much force.
Okay.
Shhh!
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Christian
Okay, I got it.
Maybe it's the other way around.
Okay, it's done.
Yes, it's perfect!
Now we'll finish the assembly by installing the largest part of the graphics board.
Finally, the last part.
Here we go.
Screws are out.
Maybe they're in.Maybe it's in there.
Hmm.
No, it's not.
It wasn't there, but now it's heavy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I worked hard to put in all the parts like this. I finished the second half of the project.
Yeah, you worked hard.
Wow!
Wow, yes!
So, now that the os is safely installed, I bought a little space for it at Animate nearby.
I bought a tiny one, because I have some space to put it. I thought a tiny one is probably the best size to put it.
Thank you very much, Aniplex!
Thank you very much for your support, so I bought Watch the Rock.
Ryo-chan
Isn't it too cute? This is really a dream
I can't do this on a regular pc, so I'm very happy!
I can see it!
I'm going to slide the lid on.
I'm in!
Wow!
It's done.
Wow.
Is that it?
Yes, it's done.
Wow, it looks good.
It looks like this.
You should try this on, right?I'd better put this on.
Then I'd like to put it on at the end.
Here we go.
Here it is!
Wow! Is it done?
Finished?
It's done!
Thank you very much.
This is how it glows.
It shines so beautifully.
And this is how the Axter I bought today looks like.
So cute!
Just what I was hoping for, oh!
I can log in.
I'm in Windows.
It's great.
So, this time, I tried my best to build my own PC,
I usually like games very much, and I've been playing games on the first PC I bought,
As I became more and more interested in games, I became more and more particular about the devices I use,
I have quite a few of them,
I have quite a few devices, but recently there are more and more cute ones for interior decoration as well,
I have a habit of collecting those kinds of things, which is unique to being a geek,
I have a habit of collecting things that only a geek would have, so it's hard for me to get involved in home-built PCs,
So I wanted to do a YouTube project on this.
It was a bit of a challenge, but I'm really happy that I was able to make it look so good and so cute.
Long day, long time,
I will use it and play with it at home for a long time.
Thank you very much. I am very happy.
Please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating.
Bye bye. Thanks for watching.Bye-bye. Thanks for watching.
Next time notice
Yes, the completed PC is well loved every day.
When I put it on, it looks like this.
You can customize the color of the inside, but I like light blue, so I'm using blue.
I also changed the inside of the PC a little bit.
The previous children are on the top.
Yes, it looked like this.
The cat is doing her best to sharpen her nails.
Thank you very much.